<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Gowra&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Gowra&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 06:00:20 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>DR KLP PUBLIC SCHOOL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/education/school/klp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 06:00:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/education/school/klp/</guid>
      <description>About Dr. Kondabolu Lakshmi Prasad Public School, Guntur Dr. Kondabolu Lakshmi Prasad Public School, also known as Dr. KLP Public School, was established in 1983. It is managed by the Nagarjuna Education Society and is affiliated with the Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE).
School Information Year of Establishment 1983 School Area 12,485 Sq. Metres Parent Institution Nagarjuna Education Society Academics Affiliation: CBSE Streams Offered: PCM, PCB &amp;amp; Arts Medium(s) of Instruction: English Classes: Nursery to 12th Gender: Co-Ed Residential Status: Boarding School No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/education/intermidiate/narayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 06:00:20 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/education/intermidiate/narayana/</guid>
      <description>About NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE BRUNDAVAN GARDEN GUNTUR NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE BRUNDAVAN GARDEN GUNTUR was established in 2012 and it is managed by the Pvt. Unaided. It is located in an Urban area within the GUNTUR block of GUNTUR district, ANDHRA PRADESH. The school offers Grades 11 to 12 and is Co-educational. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have an attached pre-primary section. The school is not using a school building as a shift-school. English is the medium of instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
